Guide to the Yale College Records of Classes
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Collected records of the Classes of 1903-1952, 1900-1973; Accession 19ND-A-403
  - Class of 1917
    - Sound film: parts I and II (no description), 1957 June (Box 91, Folder 129 - 130)
  - Class of 1919
    - "Being the story of the class of 1919 in Education": Elmore M. McKee, Secretary 1974-79, 1981 November (Box 92, Folder 131)
    - Class of 1920 - Class Book with Annotations and Loose Papers (Box 92)
  - Class of 1920s
    - Directories: Class Day, Reunions, 1920-1970 (Box 93, Folder 132)
    - Printed Matter
      - History of the Class of 1920 Sheffield Scientific School (Box 93, Folder 133)
      - Reunion material: 1st, 3rd, 6th, 15th, 20th, 1921-1940 (Box 93, Folder 134)
      - Yale Alumni Magazine: Reunions: 6th, 10th, 15th, 20th, 39th, 45th, 1935-1965 (Box 93, Folder 135)
      - Yale Graphic, 1919-1920 (Box 93, Folder 136)
    - Reunion, 6th: film, black and white, 1926 (Box 94)
    - Reunion, 10th: film, part I and II black and white, 1930 (Box 94A–94B)
    - Reunion, 15th: film, part I and II, black and white and color, 1935 (Box 94C–94D)
    - Reunion, 20th: film, part I and II, color, 1940 (Box 95, Box 95A)
    - Reunion, 30th: film, 1950 (Box 95B)
    - Reunion, 35th: film, 1955 (Box 95C)
  - Class of 1924
    - Reunion, 25th: postcard questionnaires, 1949 (Box 96, Folder 144)
  - Class of 1925
    - Reunion, 6th: register, 1931 (Box 96, Folder 145)
  - Class of 1926
    - Alumni Fund: New Haven Committee instructions, 1927-1959 (Box 96, Folder 146)
    - Certificates awarded to James Henry Oliver, 1926 June (Box 96, Folder 147)
  - Class of 1930
    - Correspondence re: questionnaires and 30 year book, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 148)
  - Class of 1931
    - Correspondence, 1928-1931 (Box 96, Folder 149 - 150)
    - Faculty reports, 1930-1931 (Box 96, Folder 151)
    - Lists, 1929-1930 (Box 97, Folder 152)
    - Receipts, 1929-1930 (Box 97, Folder 153)
  - Class of 1932
    - Notes on members of class, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 154)
    - Correspondence (E. Wright), 1960-1970 (Box 97, Folder 155)
  - Class of 1933
    - Statistics from questionnaires, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 156)
    - Statistics from questionnaires for 25th reunion, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 157)
    - Reunion, 25th: history, notes, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 158)
    - Questionnaires, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 159 - 161)
    - Questionnaires, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 162 - 164)
    - Questionnaires, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 165 - 167)
  - Class of 1952
    - Report of Military Service Kellogg Smith, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 168)
- Records of the Class of 1908, 1958-1963; Accession 2002-A-198
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
  - Record of the meeting of the class of 1908, Yale College, 1958, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Pins and hat bands from the Class of 1892, circa 1892; Accession 2005-A-068; Yale College (1887- )
  - Pins and hat bands from the Class of 1892, circa 1892 (Box 1)
- Letters of Eugene Kone, 1944; Accession 2005-A-087
  - Letters of Eugene Kone, 1944 (Box 1)
- Records of the Class of 1978, 2003; Accession 2013-A-078
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Daniel R. Kopti, 2013.
  - Letters of commemoration and proclamation on the occasion of the 25th reunion of the Yale College Class of 1978 in 2003. (Box 1)
- Records of the Class of 1939, 1972-1992; Accession 2016-A-0010
  - Class of 1939 Council and Executive Committee meeting materials, 1972-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
- Records of the Class of 1954, 2017; Accession 2018-A-0045
  General
  Volumes edited by Robert U. Redpath, III (YC '54) and Anne W. Semmes
  Gift of Russell S. Reynolds, Jr. (YC '54)
  - Published Contributions of the Yale Class of 1954: a 1954 Class Council Project - Volume I, 2017 September (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Published Contributions of the Yale Class of 1954: a 1954 Class Council Project - Volume II, 2017 September (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "1000 Voices" the Class of 1961, 2011; Accession 2019-A-0016
  Gift of Andy K. Block, Yale College Class of 1961.
  - "1000 Voices": DVD recording of interviews with the members of the Class of 1961, 2011 (Box 1)